Hello friends, I hope you are well.
After a long time and more than 2 months, I'm
back again. I want to record a video for you again
and
teach you in the simplest way possible how to configure Master HTTP Relay VPN
via your Android phone
and be able to use it.
To do this, I
suggest you download the first software, which
is Firefox, and the second
software, whose name I
cannot mention due to YouTube rules, as you can see
here, there is a keyboard that you can
use. Be
sure to download it. It is available in Fars, and it
is also available on GitHub. I will post the link on the Telegram channel
for you. You can easily activate it
and set it as the default on your keyboard
.  So now that we've done that, let's move on to
Firefox.   I
open Firefox and go to the
GitHub project called Master OTP Re-WiP on
Right from R. If you want to access it,
just search for this link or this word
in Google and open their GitHub
.  We click on it further down in the Release section at the
bottom of the page
.  So I click on the release option
.  The latest version was released 11 hours ago
.  If you know the architecture of your phone, whether it's
version 8 or 7, you'll know to
download it accordingly.  If you
don't know what your phone's architecture is, just
click on the Universal option and
download it so you can
use this software more easily without errors.  Once you
have installed it, you should return to the first page of this
project and the top where the Quick Start is
located.  I will teach you step by step
.  You can also click on the Persian quick launch
and proceed with it.
Quick Start Step What we're doing is going to
spt.google.com. I
told you to install Fox so
you can do your work here more easily.
I click on the hamburger menu option, New Project, and you
can see that nothing has been messed up and you can
easily see the entire page.
If you were to do this in Google Chrome,
a zoom mode would be performed that would make you
angry, helpless, and tired. So we did this. We go back
to the
previous page and the GitHub project
in the second part, that is, in the Quick Start section.
When we did Step One, we go to
option 4 where it is. We click on it
to see the script and codes of this project.
We click on the three dots and select Copy.
When we see the Copy option, it means the work is
done. It has been copied. There is a lot of code here that
cannot be copied on a regular keyboard. So
we came and downloaded that special keyboard,
activated it in advance, and for a moment like this
[snoring sound], we
keep our hands here.  We select the track option
.  All codes are copied.
Now that we have copied all the code, let's go to line 34
.  Where there is an asterisk, you need to
erase the text between the dot and the dot and
type whatever you want here,
but don't forget.  For example, I write "
Mabamos".
When I do this, I click on the Deploy option,
click New Deployment, click
on the Settings menu from the Select Type section,
select the first web app, it
asks for a description or new deployment for us, and we
need to write a new description for it, for example,
I write "I'll still come to mobiles", I put
Excels on AnyOne mode below,
and click Deploy.   We're
almost done.  Let's go to Access,
select Advanced, and go to the Anitel
Project.
Here I choose the Select A option and
press Continue.
Here it gives us a deployment ID that I
definitely need to copy and
keep with me.  Our work here is finished.  Now let
's go to the MHRV software that we
downloaded.  I'll open it.   I
will give him the necessary access.  In the Deployment section, I'll
paste what we just copied.  I entered the deployment ID, the
ASCII that we had typed
and that I had set as a tutorial, we put those codes on line 34,
the work is done, and here,
if we have a VPN, we definitely
disconnect it, we put the lines of Google IP detection
so that it finds the best IP for us,
we go down and click Install MIT TM
Certificate, we click Install
[snoring sound]
and we go to the settings section. In the settings, you should
look for a word called Certificate.   I
choose that CA certificate.  I'll
re-install the CIA certificate
and here I'll click the Install Anywhere option to
allow it to use this
certificate.
[Snoring sound] Our
file manager opens. I go to the Downloads folder
from the hamburger menu and scroll down. I
select the MHRB file that was created here. It's done. Now we go back to the
MHRD software. We click the Connect option.
OK and we're connected. Now we can
open filtered sites via
[Snoring sound]
Thank you very much for choosing the Mobamou channel to
watch.  I hope you enjoy this video
.  If you have any questions,
ask in the comments.  I will try to
make more videos for you in the coming days.  Until the
next video, goodbye.  Yes.